Where's the whole draft process? How far
along are you? Well, I think you know,
again, we're not close, but at the same
time a lot [music] of work was done over
the past few weeks to get the board up.
And then so much more work with our
[music] college scouts in particular of
getting to know these guys over the last
few years.
I feel really good about where we
[music] sit right now.
But there's so much we talk about it all
the time as we leave February meetings
for the combine. This isn't the end,
this is the beginning. I really get to
know these players and see who can help
the Green Bay Packers.
Do you have a favorite position to
evaluate?
>> Ooh, that's a good question.
I like it all. I will say, you know, the
>> [music]
>> offensive defensive line, they're doing
something on every play, right? There's
some positions where you might watch a
lot of tape.
>> the tax. Yeah, there's there's some
positions that maybe
they're not doing as much as others, but
in the trenches there, you better bring
it every single snap during the game. So
I do enjoy that. The experts claim
[music] the Packers have no cap room,
they cannot be active in free agency.
And yet earlier this off season, you
said we have all the flexibility
we need. Could you explain a little bit?
>> Yeah, you know, Russ does a phenomenal
job [music] of managing our cap and
predicting kind of
what's going to come, you know, ahead
and and making sure we're ready and
prepared for all that. And and again, I
think [music] there's always challenges
every year.
But like most all years, Russ has got us
in a position of flexibility that we can
attack
>> [music]
>> whatever we need to attack to help this
team. The
experts say the Packers need help at
corner,
in the defensive line inside, and in
[music] the offensive line.
Are they on the right track? We need
help everywhere because that's that's
the nature of [music] our game. It's a
changing game. We need help at every
spot. I like the group that we have in
those positions and I think they're more
than capable,
but that doesn't mean we're not going to
add
>> [music]
>> competition to those rooms. And I'm
excited about some of the early looks at
some of these players particularly in
the draft and free agency that could
help us.
Want to talk to you about a [music]
couple of your recent first rounders.
Matthew Golden.
Watching him during training camp last
year, somebody,
>> [music]
>> a football person, asked me if you
absolutely had to have a reception, had
to have a guy get open, who [music]
would it be? And I said Matthew Golden.
Now, his regular season didn't play out
that way, [music]
but he's still a young fellow with a
mystical it, is he not?
>> Yeah. I think, you know, again, you
know, sometimes players only have so
much to say over the opportunities they
have. And I thought the opportunities
that Matthew got, you know, he performed
at a very, very high level
starting in training camp all through
the season. So I know he [music] would
have liked more and I would expect that
going into the season he's going to have
more.
We're excited about what he can do for
the team next year. And what's it going
to take for Jordan Morgan to fulfill
his wealth
of resources and potential?
>> Yeah. I think again, just opportunity
getting out there and being able to
play. I know a lot of it has been made
about him moving around. His versatility
has helped us a tremendous amount over
the last couple years.
I do think as he solidifies into a one
spot, you'll see [music] his best. The
Packers football leadership, yourself,
Matt [music] LaFleur, Russ Ball, it will
remain intact
for the long term. [music]
What does that continuity do for you?
>> Yeah. I think it just gives us the
consistency of having a better chance
year in and year out because we've been
together for a [music] while, we know
each other. And I think our goals are
all the same. We're very aligned in what
we're trying to accomplish. I think that
is very helpful because I have people
that I can count on for support. That is
not the standard everywhere else.
>> [music]